export const questionsQuiz1=[{question: "What was the first Pokémon ever created?",
                 answer: "Rhydon",
                 options: ["Pikachu", "Bulbasaur", "Mew"]
                },{question: "Which Pokémon is known as the “Eon Pokémon”?",
                    answer: "Latios and Latias",
                    options: ["Lugia", "Mewtwo", "Rayquaza"]
                },{question: "What type is the Pokémon “Garchomp”?",
                    answer: "Dragon/Ground",
                    options: ["Dragon/Flying", "Ground/Rock", "Dragon/Steel"]
                },{question: "In which generation was the Fairy-type introduced?",
                    answer: "Generation VI",
                    options: ["Generation IV", "Generation V", "Generation VII"]
                },{question: "Which of the following Pokémon is not a Legendary Pokémon?",
                    answer: "Garchomp",
                    options: ["Entei", "Regirock", "Cresselia"]
                },{question: "What is the name of the region in Pokémon Sun and Moon?",
                    answer: "Alola",
                    options: ["Sinnoh", "Hoenn", "Unova"]
                },{question: "Which Pokémon can evolve into multiple different forms depending on certain conditions?",
                    answer: "Eevee",
                    options: ["Pikachu", "Mew", "Ditto"]
                },{question: "What move does the most damage to a Ghost-type Pokémon?",
                    answer: "Crunch",
                    options: ["Psychic", "Shadow Ball", "Hyper Beam"]
                },{question: "Which Pokémon is known for having the signature move “Spacial Rend”?",
                    answer: "Palkia",
                    options: ["Dialga", "Giratina", "Arceus"]
                },{question: "Who is the current champion of the Galar region in Pokémon Sword and Shield?",
                    answer: "Leon",
                    options: ["Hop", "Bea", "Raihan"]
                }];

export const questionsQuiz2=[{question: "What is the evolutionary form of Porygon-Z?",
                 answer: "None, Porygon-Z is the final form",
                 options: ["Porygon2", "Porygon", "Porygon-X"]
                },{question: "Which Pokémon’s cry is the longest in the games?",
                    answer: "Kricketune",
                    options: ["Jynx", "Wailord", "Palkia"]
                },{question: "What is the signature move of the Pokémon Aegislash?",
                    answer: "King’s Shield",
                    options: [" Sacred Sword", "Iron Head", "Shadow Claw"]
                },{question: "What is the only Pokémon that can learn the move “Dragon Ascent”?",
                    answer: "Rayquaza",
                    options: ["Garchomp", "Dragonite", "Salamence"]
                },{question: "What are the two types of the Pokémon Giratina in its Altered Forme?",
                    answer: "Ghost/Dragon",
                    options: ["Dragon/Flying", "Ghost/Flying", "Ghost/Dark"]
                },{question: "Which Pokémon has a Gigantamax form that turns into a skyscraper-like structure?",
                    answer: "Duraludon",
                    options: ["Coalossal", "Copperajah", "Corviknight"]
                },{question: "What is the main Legendary Pokémon in Pokémon X?",
                    answer: "Xerneas",
                    options: ["Yveltal", "Zygarde", "Diancie"]
                },{question: "Which Pokémon can Mega Evolve into Mega Garchomp?",
                    answer: "Garchomp",
                    options: ["None, Garchomp cannot Mega Evolve", "Gible", "Gabite"]
                },{question: "Which Pokémon is known as the “Battle Bond” form when it bonds with its Trainer?",
                    answer: "Ash-Greninja",
                    options: ["Charizard", "Lucario", "Pikachu"]
                },{question: "What is the effect of the move “Spore”?",
                    answer: "Puts the target to sleep",
                    options: ["Reduces the target’s Speed", "Poisons the target", "Paralyzes the target"]
                }];